SHAUN KOLICH

1012 Vizcaya Lakes Rd | Ocoee, Florida, 34761 | (407) 486-8060 | shaun.kolich@gmail.com

Professional Skills

React JS

Git

Node IS

ISON

CSS3

SOL Lite3

Bootstrap

LESS

Redux

Express

Database Creation

Javascript

Libraries

Rest API's

Web UI

Summary

Hard-working professional with 13+ years of experience and a proven knowledge of project lifecycle, troubleshooting, and desktop technology. Aiming to leverage my skills to successfully fill the Full Stack Web Developer role at your company. Git Hub – https://github.com/ShaunKolich LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/shaun-kolich-98517450/

Education

LAMBDA SCHOOL, Silicon Valley, CA

, Enrolled March 2020

Full Stack Web Development Candidate (Expected graduation Mar 2020)

UNIVERSITY OF PHOENIX, Phoenix, Arizona

A.A., Graduated March 2013

Completed coursework towards A.A. Software Engineering (Mar 2013)

Employment History

Self Employed

PRESIDENT, November 2018 - Present

- · Advised customers on technological needs to improve their business.
- · Advised clients on appropriate web development opportunities and technologies.

BrightHouse Networks

HELP DESK, March 2013 - March 2017

- · Resolved network connectivity issues for small and medium-sized businesses and handled escalation calls.
- · Saved the company 10,000's of dollars by troubleshooting and deescalating and solving FCC Escalations.

US Navy

PETTY OFFICER - MANAGEMENT, October 2004 - October 2012

- In my role as Torpedo Man 2nd Class, my main responsibility was in ensuring the weapons were up to inspection and ready to fire if ordered to do so.
- · Saved the Navy over \$20,000 in repairs of damage control equipment by correcting over 75 inspection discrepancies leading to 98% scores on two damage control inspections, and ensured the USS Eisenhower was "battle-ready."